Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
（鉄男(てつお)）フッ…
ああ もしもし 岩城(いわき)さんッスか？
ヘヘヘッ… 俺ッスよ
Oh, hi.
Is this Mr. Iwaki?
Heh, yeah it's me.
ええ…
ちょっと いい物(もん) 手に入って
Yeah...
I got some pretty cool stuff to show you...
Goodbye
Yeah, I have money.
（計(けい)）ああ 金なら あるよ
（計）うん？ 行ってる 行ってる
ちゃんと行ってるって
Huh? Of course I've been going.
No, I haven't been skipping class!
Okay, I gotta go or I'll be late.
ああ… じゃ 遅刻するから
She thinks I'll be fine as long
as she gives me money.
（計）金さえ持たせときゃいいって
思ってんだからな　…たく
Jeez...
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
（リポーター）ご覧ください
The apartment building you see here
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
このアパートはバブル崩壊後
持ち主不在となり―
Has been abandoned since the collapse
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
取り壊されずに
放置されていた物です
Of the bubble economy at the end of the 1980s.
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
昨夜 突然 崩れ去ったらしく
このような いわゆる廃屋の…
Apparently it suddenly collapsed last night.
The incident is expected to ignite further debate
Was that your mother on the phone?
（岸本(きしもと)）電話 お母さん？
（計）ああ
Over what actions should be taken
Was that your mother on the phone?
With regard to derelict buildings like this...
Yeah.
What did she say?
何て？
（計）別に…
With regard to derelict buildings like this...
Why did a derelict building
Oh, nothing.
She feels she has to call me every now and then.
時々
義務っぽく かけてくるだけだよ
Suddenly collapse for no apparent reason?
She feels she has to call me every now and then.
（岸本）ふ～ん…
Suddenly collapse for no apparent reason?
Hmm...
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
（リポーター）そして
更に 倒壊したアパートから―
The second story roof of a residence located
about 200 meters from the apartment building
On the brink of disaster: BUILDING COLLAPSES!
200メートルほど離れた民家でも
同時刻に２階の屋根が…
The second story roof of a residence located
about 200 meters from the apartment building
also collapsed around the same time.
Also collapsed around the same time.
What was THAT about last night?
（計）
ゆうべの あれは 何だったんだよ？
What was THAT about last night?
あんなに いい感じだったのにな…
I thought we'd become at least a little closer...
あっ… もっとも あれか
Oh well, we did it to save Kato anyway...
加藤(かとう) 助けるために
やったんだもんな　くそ…
Dammit.
（司会）さて
当番組では追跡リポートとして―
We have been following the story of two high
school boys who went missing in the subway,
Dammit.
We have been following the story of two high
school boys who went missing in the subway,
“消えたヘアヌード写真集の
高校生の謎”を取材してきましたが
leaving behind nothing but an adult magazine.
Leaving behind nothing but an adult magazine.
Man, they're still talking about that?
（計）まだやってんのかよ
Now, the latest news on that story...
Man, they're still talking about that?
And now it's become the high school students
"with the adult magazine"!
しかも いつの間にか―
“ヘアヌード写真集の高校生”に
なってるし…
They're talking about you, right?
あれ 玄野(くろの)君だよね？
ウッ…
（岸本）やっぱり
I knew it...
加藤君
そういう本 持ってなさそうだもん
I didn't think Kato would be
reading those things...
Oh, and how do you know?
そんなこと分かるかよ
だって 弟さんと一緒に 親戚の家に
間借りしてるんでしょう？
Because he's staying at a relative's house
with his little brother, right?
きっと 持ってないわ
I don't think he has stuff like that.
What makes you so sure?
（計）なんで そうなるんだよ？
Kato must have a lot of stuff to worry about.
（岸本）加藤君 大変だよね
弟さんの世話して…
He has to take care of his brother,
あのマンションに来たら
今度は みんなの心配して
and then when we're all at that apartment
he worries about us so much...
I guess he's just a really caring guy.
優しいっていうか 何ていうか…
ただの世話好きだよ
（岸本）そんな言い方しないでよ
He just likes to butt in on
everyone's business, that's all.
Don't you talk about him that way!
If it weren't for him,
加藤君がいなかったら
みんな どうなってたか
where would we all be now, huh?
Yeah, but I'm the one who
was able to pull the trigger...
撃ったのは俺だけど
（岸本）それは そうだけど…
Yeah, that's true... But, still...
Now that I've been there twice,
I understand something really well.
（計）
２回行ってみて よく分かったよ
あそこじゃ… あの世界じゃ
優しいだけじゃ生き残れない
Being caring isn't enough to survive there...
Kato can talk all he wants about
all of us going back together,
いくら加藤が
“みんなで帰ろう”って言ったって
but it's not that easy.
そう うまくいかないって…
Yeah, I guess you're right...
（岸本）そうだね　私も そう思う
I think so, too.
えっ？
（岸本）ホント そう思うよ
I really do agree with you.
Well, that was good.
ごちそうさまでした
な… 何なんだよ？
What the heck's with her?
Fresh Mix Sandwich 170 yen
Total 170 yen
Paid 200 yen
CHANGE DUE 30 yen
（店員）ありがとうございました
Fresh Mix Sandwich 170 yen
Total 170 yen
Paid 200 yen
CHANGE DUE 30 yen
Thank you.
Fresh Mix Sandwich 170 yen
Total 170 yen
Paid 200 yen
CHANGE DUE 30 yen
Look what you've done!
（加藤の叔母）なんて子だい！
I won't let you get away with this!
（叔母）もう許さないよ！
こいつ なにが“朝ご飯”なのよ！
How dare you ask me for breakfast!
I know you came in the house yesterday
with your shoes all muddy again!
昨日 また泥だらけの靴で
玄関に入ったでしょう？
The foyer is a mess!
（叔母）
三和土(たたき)が泥だらけじゃないの！
Ayumu!
（加藤）
歩(あゆむ)！ 歩が何かしましたか？
Did he do something?
This good for nothing kid has the nerve
to ask me for breakfast after what he did!
（叔母）
やっかい者が朝ご飯ねだるなんて
ずうずうしいって言ってんのよ
What do you think? Am I wrong here?
ええ？ 違う？ 違うかい？
（殴る音）
違うなら言ってみな！ ンッ！
If you think I'm wrong,
why don't you say something?!
どうだい？ 答えてみなよ！
（歩）ごめんなさい…
Well? Answer me!
I have nothing to feed either of you!
あんたらに食べさせるメシなんか
ないんだよ！
I just bought breakfast for Ayumu, so...
（加藤）歩の朝メシなら
買ってきましたから… だから…
Shut up!
（叔母）うるさいよ！
（殴る音）
Please stop! That's enough...
（加藤）お願いです　もう…
（叔母）えっ？ 何だい？
Huh? Did you just say something?
Are you planning to give me lip?
言い返す気かい？
Please stop it.
やめてください…
（叔母）反抗するのかい？
お前 何さまのつもりだい！ ええ？
Are you defying me?
Who the hell do you think you are? Eh?
Stop it...
やめろ…
（叔母）フン… 何だい？ その目は
What kind of look is that?
（加藤）もう やめてくれ
Please stop it!
これ以上 歩に手を上げたら…
上げたら…
If you hit him one more time... I'II...
What are...
何を…
If you keep it up...
これ以上やったら
俺 何するか分かんねえ
I don't know what I might do!
（歩）
兄ちゃん！ やめて！ もういいよ
Stop it, big brother!
That's enough! Please, just stop!
お願いだから やめて
で… 出ていけ…
お前たちなんか とっとと出てけ！
Get... get out!
Both of you, get the hell
out of this house, now!
（歩）ウッ…
（加藤）そ… そうします
We... we'll do that.
（教師）
ＡＣ＝１とすると ＢＣ＝ルート３
When AC equal 1,
BC equal root 3...
（計）あっ… 岸本
Kishimoto...
BC equal root 3...
加藤君 １人でも死なせないように
頑張ってた
He was trying his hardest,
not letting even one person die...
他人の命を
分け隔てなく大切にする人なのよ
Kato's the kind of guy who values
the lives of everyone around him equally.
Crap... Here we go again.
またかよ おい…
う… うわ！
（岸本）優しくて強くて…
He's caring and strong... like no other...
あんな人いない
うん あんな人いないよ
That's right... He's like no other.
What the hell is this?
（計）何だっつうんだよ
そんな格好で 何言ってんだよ！
What is she talking about
looking like THAT?
180 degrees...
Excuse me!
（女子生徒）先生
（教師）なに？
Yes?
玄野 また勃(た)ってま～す
（計）なっ…
Kurono's got a hard on again!
Kurono... Again?
（教師）玄野君 またなの？
（女子生徒）やらしい
（女子生徒）変態
Hoo, boy...
Excuse me.
（聖(せい)）あの…
（店主）ああ ごめんなさい
Oh, pardon me.
That same guy stole our books again...
いや また いつものヤツに
本 取られちゃってね　ハァ…
Supposedly, he's been selling
the books he shoplifts.
いや 盗んで そのまま
売ってるみたいなんですけどね
…で 何か？
Well now, how can I help you?
Have you got the book
I ordered the other day?
（聖）
この間 注文した本 届いてます？
Oh, let me check...
ああ ちょっとお待ちを…
What's your name, Ma'am?
え～ お名前は？
（聖）桜丘(さくらおか)です　桜丘聖
Sakuraoka.
Sei Sakuraoka.
Wow, what a pretty name...
（岸本）
へえ… きれいな響きの名前
I wonder what kanji she uses to write it.
どういう字 書くんだろう？
Let me see... Oh, this one.
（店主）え～っと… あっ これね
Miranda Foster's Labyrinth, right?
ミランダ・フォスターの
「迷宮」でしょう？
いや すいません　まだなんですよ
Ah, I'm sorry. Looks like it hasn't come in yet.
It's kind of hard to get it in since they never did
another printing after the first edition...
初版以来
増刷されてないんで なかなか…
いつごろ入ります？
Do you have any idea when
you'll be able to get it?
Hmm... Hopefully by the end of next week.
そうだな…
多分 来週の後半ぐらいには
I'll call you when it comes in.
あっ 入ったら お電話しますから
（聖）じゃ お願いします
That'd be great. Thanks.
It's a frickin' toy!
（岩城）おもちゃじゃねえかよ
（鉄男）ヘヘッ… 違(ちげ)えッスよ
No it's not.
Where'd you get it?
（岩城）どこで手に入れた？
Well, it's kind of a long story...
（鉄男）あ～…
それが ちょっと ややこしくって
Long story?
（岩城）
ややこしいって… フン… こんな物
Hah! This piece of shit?
ウワッ… 今月は
金の代わりに それでっつうことで
Can I use it as the payment for this month?
You know, like instead of money?
You shittin' me?
（岩城）てめえ 本気か？
こんな物 要るか バカ！
Who the hell'd want this
piece of garbage, ya moron!
So, are you saying, "No"?
（鉄男）ダメっすかね？
What, you ain't got the money?
Eh? C'mon, give it up!
（岩城）
金持ってきてねえのか？ 金！
早(は)よ出せや　ああ？
You planning on taking it to the grave?
冥土に持ってくんスか？
（岩城）ああ？ 今 何つった？
Huh? What did you just say?
You don't need money.
Cuz' you'll be dead real soon.
金なんか もう要らないっしょ
もうすぐ死ぬんだから
No one can fuck with me now!
俺は 最強だぜ！
Hey, you'll fall if you keep running
around like that! Come on, be careful!
（母親）ほら そんなに走っちゃ
危ないわよ！ ほら 気をつけて
（母親）
ほら もう そろそろ帰りますよ
Okay, time to go home!
This is it.
（加藤）ここだ
（歩）えっ？
I saved up enough money for it
working part-time.
（加藤）バイトして金ためてたんだ
今日から ここが 俺たちの家(うち)だ
This is our home from now on.
Yay! We did it! We did it!
やったー！ やった やった！
I'm sorry, Ayumu...
ごめんな 歩
（歩）えっ 何が？
Huh? About what?
もっと早く金たまってれば…
If only I could've saved up sooner...
大丈夫だって！
今日から もう殴られないし
Hey, it's alright!
From today on I don't need to
put up with her hitting me...
That's all it matters.
それでいいじゃん
ホントに ごめん…
I'm so...
（歩）頑張ろうぜ 兄ちゃん！
僕も すぐ働くからさ！
Let's make it together, big bro!
I'll get a job soon, too!
Don't be silly! You have to go to school!
（加藤）バカ 学校行けっつうの
Hey, how about our futons?
（歩）あっ 布団はどうするの？
（加藤）
友達が古くなった布団くれるんだ
取りに行かねえと
My friend has a couple of
old futons he'll give us.
I need to go get them now.
I'm coming, too.
（歩）僕も行くよ
１人じゃ重いでしょう？
They're too heavy for you to
carry by yourself, aren't they?
I'll be fine.
大丈夫だって
歩はテレビ見てろって
You stay home and watch TV.
You've been wanting
to watch some anime, right?
アニメ見たかったんだろう？
（歩）えっ いいの？
Can I really?!
今日から毎日 見ていいんだ
（歩）うん！ ヒヒッ！
Yup. Now you can watch it
everyday if you want to!
Thanks!
Here's the change.
（岸本）はい 今のおつり
You know, I can cook as long
as it's nothing fancy.
私 簡単な料理なら作れるよ
It's too expensive to keep buying
dinner at the convenience stores.
いつまでもコンビニのお弁当じゃ
高くつくし…
Don't worry about it.
いいよ 別に
It's not like we're
living together or anything...
（計）俺たち
同棲(どうせい)してるわけじゃないもんな
あしたから作ろうか？
（計）いいって！
Do you want me to
start cooking tomorrow?
I said it's okay!
Why are you so mad?
なに怒ってんの？
（計）怒ってない
I'm not mad.
怒ってるよ 玄野君
Yes you are, Kurono.
I bet you wouldn't be bugging me
like this if I were Kato!
（計）加藤になら
そんな突っ込み しないくせに
（加藤）良かった　まだあった
Great.
OVERSIZED
TRASH
DO NOTLEAVE TRASH
Great.
OVERSIZED
TRASH
DO NOTLEAVE TRASH
They're still here.
OVERSIZED
TRASH
DO NOTLEAVE TRASH
I'll be making a little more money
starting next month, so...
（鉄男）来月から
もうちょっと金増えっからさ
Really?
（妻）そう
（鉄男）
引っ越すか？ もっと でかい家に
You wanna move? To a bigger place?
We don't have that kind of money.
（妻）そんな金ないじゃん
（鉄男）
ヘヘッ… なんとかなるって
We'll be fine.
（妻）ふ～ん…
Right...
Hey!
（鉄男）
おい いいかげんにしろよ てめえ
Cut the bullshit!
何が？
（鉄男）乳も出ないのに―
What?
What the hell are you doing?
You know you're not producing milk!
何やってんだよ？
しょうがないじゃん！
タバコは買ってきても―
What else am I gonna do?!
You'll buy yourself cigarettes
but never buy milk for the baby!
牛乳買ってこない
バカ亭主のせいなんだから
It's all my stupid husband's fault!
What did you just say?
おい 今 何つった？
（妻）建設現場から電話あった
I got a call from the
construction site.
They said none of you
showed up for work.
あんたら 誰も来ないって…
もう来なくていいってさ
They also said not to bother coming anymore.
あっ…
（妻）最低　４人ともクビだってさ
Pathetic...
They fired all four of you!
傘も友達がくれたの？
（加藤）うん？ ああ…
You got this umbrella from your friend, too?
Uh, yeah...
You got nice friends.
いい友達だね
（加藤）そうだな
I guess so...
Okay, it's all done! Look!
できたぞ ほら
Cool! A. K!
（歩）やったー！ “Ａ・Ｋ”だ
I spent almost all the money
getting this place.
（加藤）この部屋借りるんで
ほとんど金なくなっちゃったけどな
また ためるから
But I'll start saving up again.
今日は これと一緒に寝るよ
（加藤）雨の夢見るぞ
I'm gonna sleep with this tonight.
Then you'll dream about the rain.
That's okay.
（歩）いいよ それでも！
早く雨降んないかなぁ
Now I can't wait for it to rain!
Okay, I'm going to sleep.
兄ちゃん
（加藤）ハッ…
じゃ 寝るよ
Ayumu.
歩…
（歩）なに？
What?
Uh... Never mind.
（加藤）いや… 何でもない
昼間 本屋さんで暇つぶしてたら
すごくきれいな人 見かけたの
I saw this beautiful girl when I was
killing time at the bookstore this afternoon.
はぁ？ 知るかよ そんなの
Huh? What the heck do I care?
Her name was Sei Sakuraoka.
“桜丘聖さん”っていうんだって
「迷宮」って本 注文してるみたい
It looked like she had ordered
some book called Labyrinth.
How about that...
（計）ふ～ん…
All I've been reading are study guides
and story collections of masterworks.
（岸本）
今まで 参考書とか名作全集とか
そういうのばっかりで
どんな本なのかなって
So it made me wonder what
kind of book this Labyrinth is...
Hey, Kurono, do you read books like that?
玄野君 そういう本読んだりする？
Not really.
読まねえ　あんま興味ねえし
I'm not really into that stuff.
I wonder how Kato's doing...
加藤君 どうしてるかな？
What are you talking about?
てめえ 何言ってんだ？
別に“走りやめろ”とは言わないよ
どうせ言ったって聞かないんだから
I'm not saying I want you
to give up your bike.
And even if I did, you'd never
listen to me anyway.
Where were you last night?
What were you doing?
ゆうべ どこで何してた？
（鉄男）何って…
What do you mean?
いつになっても
牛乳買ってこないから―
You never came back after
you went to get milk!
何回も携帯かけたんだからね！
なんで電源切ってたんだよ？
I don't know how many times
I tried calling you on your cell!
Why did you turn off your phone?
I was out of area!
（鉄男）通じねえ所にいたんだよ
Yeah, right!
（妻）ああ そう　どうせ ひと晩中
春哉たちと女マワしてたんだろう？
I bet you were out fucking around
with your boy Haruya again.
All your buddies' cell phones
were off last night, too!
あいつらも
みんな電源切ってたからね
That's not what I was doing!
（鉄男）俺は そんなことしてねえ
じゃ なんで電源切ってたんだよ？
（鉄男）説明したって分かんねえよ
Then why did you turn off your phone?
Even if I explained it to you,
you wouldn't understand!
ふざけんな！
（鉄男）てめえこそ ふざけんな！
Don't give me that bullshit!
No! Don't you give me your bullshit!
俺は… 俺は ひと晩中な…
I... I spent the whole damn night...
So there were that many good-looking
girls out there, huh?! Is that it?
（妻）そんなに いい女が
いっぱいいたってか？ ああ？
（岸本）やっぱり大変だよ 加藤君
I bet Kato has a lot to worry about.
Give me a break!
あのなぁ… 今朝は ちょびっと
俺の意見に賛成したじゃねえかよ
You were acting like you agreed
with me a little this morning!
He was trying really hard
so all of us could survive...
（岸本）加藤君 １人でも
死なせないように頑張ってた
But if you think about it, he didn't
end up being all that helpful...
（計）
でもさ 加藤 何だかんだ言っても
あんまり役に立ってねえんだよな
なに？ なんで そんなこと言うの？
そんなことないよ！
What? Why do you say stuff like that?
It's not true!
Oh yeah?
（計）そうか？
（岸本）
きっと あるんだよ この世の中って
There's one for every person in this world...
何が？
（岸本）役割分担みたいなもの
One what?
I'm saying everyone has some role to play.
What?
Like how you beat the aliens
（岸本）玄野君が敵を倒して…
while Kato concentrated on protecting everyone.
でも 加藤君は
みんなを守ることに専念してとか
I mean things like that.
（計）何だよ それ
Whatever...
I think that... both of you are great.
（岸本）
私 どっちも すごいって思う
Kato's the kind of guy who values
the lives of everyone around him equally.
加藤君は 他人の命を
分け隔てなく大切にする人なのよ
He's caring and strong... like no other.
（岸本）優しくて 強くて
あんな人いない…
うん あんな人いないよ
Yeah, he's different from everyone else.
What the hell are you trying to say?!
何だっつうんだよ…
（岸本）えっ？
What?
What the hell are you trying to say!
何だっつうんだよ！
What the hell is your problem?
何だっつうんだ！ てめえなぁ…
You say all that just because you
couldn't reach me for one frickin' night?
ちょっと ひと晩
携帯つながんなかっただけで―
そこまで言うか？ 普通　ああ？
何にもしてないっていうんなら
証明してみなよ！ ええ？ ああ？
Fine! Prove you weren't out doing anything
like that last night! Well? Can you?
I was...
俺は 俺はな… 俺は！
I was... just...
なに？ それ
What the heck is that?
おもちゃ振り回して
なに粋がってんの？
Trying to intimidate me with a toy gun?
You're so stupid!
バカじゃないの？
Bitch! I'll fuckin' kill you!
てめえ 殺すぞ！
Okay, go ahead! Shoot me! C'mon!
やればいいじゃん！
撃ちなって！ ほら！
This is bullshit!
冗談じゃないよ　あしたから
どうやって暮らすのさ？
How are we supposed to live
with no money?
Who's going to give a lowlife biker
like you a job in this economy?
この不景気に あんたらみたいな
ゾク 雇ってくれる現場あんの？
ほら
あるなら言ってみなって　ほら！
C'mon, answer me! C'mon!
Make up your mind, will you?
（計）どっちかにしろよ！
何だよ 中途半端でさぁ
You're so indecisive, you know that?
I didn't mean to sound that way...
えっ… 私
そういうつもりで言ったんじゃ…
You move into my place right out of the blue,
but you don't even let me touch you!
（計）いきなり俺ん家に
転がり込んできて 何もさせねえし
“加藤君 加藤君 加藤君”！
It's always Kato, Kato, Kato!
（岸本）ちょ… ちょっと 玄野君？
Wait a minute...
Kato! Kato!
“加藤 加藤”！
I knew what you were thinking last night
when you asked Kato if he lives by himself.
あれだろう？ ゆうべ 加藤に
１人暮らしか聞いてただろう？
Okay... And so what?
だったら何よ？
あれって ホントは俺とじゃなくて
あいつと住みたいんだろう？
You were asking because you wanted
to live with him, not me, right?
そんなこと言ってないじゃない
I didn't say that.
言ってるのも同然なんだよ！
都合よく利用しやがって
You might as well have!
You're just using me!
ふざけんじゃねえっつうの！
何だよ 俺は…
Give me a break!
What the hell am I doing with you anyway?
Get out! Just get out now!
出てけよ！ 今すぐ出てけ！
何なんだよ 俺は…
What the hell am I doing?
I'm letting you stay here and
eat my food for free!
タダでメシ食わせて
間借りさせてやって
I'm a complete fool!
すごいお人よしか 俺は！
You're right...
そうだよね　やっぱり
勉強ばっかりしててもダメなんだ
Keeping up my scores at school
doesn't mean anything, I guess...
I don't understand how
the world works at all...
（岸本）世の中のこと
何も分かってないもん 私
I guess it's not like cooking for you
will make it all better. Will it?
ご飯作ってあげれば
いいってもんじゃないんだよね
やべえ 言い過ぎた… どうしよう
Shit, I crossed the line...
What should I do now?
You're right, Kurono.
玄野君の言うとおりなの…
I know things can't be that convenient.
そんな虫のいい話
あるわけないんだもん
Whoa, hold on!
えっ… ちょっと ちょっと…
（岸本）
でも １つだけ分かってほしいの
But there's one thing
I want you to understand.
I...
私… 玄野君 すごいって思ってる
I really do think you're great.
What?
な… なに？
（岸本）ホントに
加藤君とは感じが違うけど…
I'm serious.
You're a lot different from Kato,
but... well...
けど…
Shit... What do I do now?
ヤバイ　どうしたらいいんだよ？
Hey, it's that same dude from the other day...
（暴走族）おい こいつ この間の
（暴走族）ああ 牛乳野郎だ
Oh, yeah! The milk guy, right?
（暴走族）
ヘヘッ… こいつ 幽霊かよ
Is he a ghost or something?
（鉄男）俺は 何のために…
What am I doing this for?
That's one dumb daddy, huh?
バカなお父ちゃんだよね
（暴走族）ハハッ… アホだ こいつ
それ おもちゃじゃねえかよ
Look at this dumbass! That's a toy!
Moron!
（暴走族）バカじゃねえの？
（暴走族）よし もう１回 殺しとけ
Hey, let's kill him one more time!
（鉄男）
教えろ　俺は一体 何なんだよ？
Why? What the hell am I doing?
Tell me why, Gantz!
教えろ ガンツーッ！
Do you think there's like a bomb or
something planted in each of our heads?
（岸本）
もしかして 全員 頭の中に 何か
爆弾みたいなの入ってるのかな？
Gantz? What the hell is that?
（暴走族）
“ガンツ”だ？ 何だ？ そりゃ
Huh? What the hell's with him?
（暴走族）
どうしたんだよ？ こいつ
Hey! I'm lactating! I can breastfeed now!
（妻）ちょっと
出たんだよ おっぱい！ 母乳！
Come home right now! I can feed our baby!
すぐ帰ってきて　出たんだってば！
No need for me anymore then...
俺は 用済みじゃねえかよ…
I'm sorry...
（岸本）ごめん… ごめんね
私… 私 出ていくから
I'm sorry...
I'II... I'll move out.
Thank you for everything. Goodbye.
ありがとう 今まで… さようなら
But there's one thing
I want you to understand.
（岸本）
でも ひとつだけ分かってほしいの
私… 玄野君 すごいって思ってる
I... I really do think you're great.
I'm serious.
本当に 加藤君とは
感じが違うけど… けど…
You're a lot different from Kato,
but... well...
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
（聖）
ガンツ 開かない窓 開かない玄関
Gantz, locked windows, locked doors,
Tokyo Tower, strange people, an annoying song,
東京タワー 妙な人々
ウザイ歌 泣いてる男の子
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
Gantz, locked windows, locked doors,
Tokyo Tower, strange people, an annoying song,
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
A crying boy, a fearful girl and me...
a crying boy, a fearful girl and me...
おびえてる女の子　そして私は…
Next time: "I Wanna Be There Now!"
次回 “早くイキてぇ！”